I’m sure that you don’t believe
In the being whose dreams were endless
I’m sure that fear won’t let you believe
There’s someone talking to you in your heart
But even then, you never believe
Foolish... Your heart is locked up tight
You’re only driving me to become a wicked witch
“Ahh... The miracle I dreamed with him was stolen away”
But you feel it too, don’t you?
Those must be our eyes
Your dreams won’t come true
It’s karma for forever averting your gaze
Fright makes your disbelief stronger
The person beside you sees into your dirty mind
No miracle will ever occur
Neither your dreams nor the gold you sought out
Your little eyes with nothing inside can only see so much
“Uu... I can’t ‘see’ the childhood days I spent with him”
You can hear something right now, can’t you?
Those must be our screams
Reigning   Reigning   The spiral Venus
Over all the little people
Burning   Burning   Burn it in the magic and...
Burn it to the ground   Only
Fear me   Fear me   “The heartless breaker”
Every single one of you, I’ll
Take you   Take to   the end of the world
Come now, one and all